Inventory of the Francis Burton Harrison Papers 1786-1932
Earl Gregg Swem Library, College of William and Mary
Special Collections, Earl Gregg Swem Library, College of William and Mary
Francis Burton Harrison Papers, 1786-1932.
Special Collections, Earl Gregg Swem Library, College of William and Mary
Mss. 65 H26
579 items.
Papers collected by Francis Burton Harrison. Chiefly typescripts of letters, 1786-1840, of members of the Harrison family. Also includes notes for The Harrisons of Skimino.
Harrison Family,; Francis Burton Harrison.
Administrative Information
Restrictions on Access
Collection is open to all researchers.
Acquisition Information
Gift: 579 items, 12/15/1941, 2/3/1942.
Biographical/Historical Information
Francis Burton Harrison was born in New York City 18 December 1873. He was the son of Burton Harrison and Constance (Cary) Harrison and the brother of Fairfax Harrison. He graduated from Yale University in 1895 and from the New York Law School. He served in the Spanish-American War and in Congress from 1907-1913. Harrison was governor-general of the Philippines 1913-1921. He lived in Scotland from 1921-1934. He served as advisor to the governors of the Philippines. Harrison died in Flemington, New Jersey, 21 November 1957. He was the author of Archibald Cary of Carysbrook, Aris Sonis Focisque (The Harrisons of Skimino), Burton Chronicles of Colonial Virginia, The Corner-stone of Philippine Independence, and a Selection of the Letters of Fairfax Harrison.
Scope and Content Information
Papers, 1786-1932, collected by Francis Burton Harrison. Chiefly typescripts of letters, 1786-1840, of members of the Harrison family, includes notes for The Harrisons of Skimino.
This group of typescripts, letters, and notes was collected by Francis Burton Harrison for the publication of The Harrisons of Skimino edited by his brother Fairfax Harrison. Box 1 contains typescripts of Harrison family letters and a few original manuscripts. Box 2 includes notes for The Harrisons of Skimino, correspondence between Fairfax and Francis Burton Harrison, material relating to the Gale family and to Pocahontas.
Arrangement
Organization
This collection is organized into series. Series 1 includes typescripts of Harrison family letters; Series 2 includes orginial manuscripts for The Harrisons of Skimino; Series 3 includes notes on source material for The Harrisons of Skimino; Series 4 includes miscellaneous notes and materials.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged in chronological order by date.
Additional Descriptive Data
Bibliography
Harrison, Fairfax. Aris Sonis Focisque, Being A Memoir Of An American Family, The Harrisons Of Skimino, And Particularly Of Jesse Burton Harrison And Burton Norvell Harrison. 1910.
Call Number: CS71 .H32 1910
Related Materials
The papers of Fairfax Harrison, who is the brother of Francis Burton Harrison, are also located within Swem Library. These papers, 1736-1945, were produced and collected by Fairfax Harrison, and include his correspondence with individuals and institutions concerning his interest in Virginia History.
Fairfax Harrison Papers, Manuscripts and Rare Books Department, Swem Library, College of William and Mary.
Fairfax Harrison Papers, 1736- 1945. 6,116 items. Collection number: Mss. 65 H25
Index Terms
Family Names:
Harrison Family.
Components List
  Series 1: Typescripts of Harrison Family Letters
- Typescripts of Harrison Family Letters, 1786-1889, n.d. (Box-folder 1:1-10)
  - Letters, 1986-1989., 7 items. (Box-folder 1:1)
    - Christopher Anthony, [n.p.] to William Harrison, Ja[me]s City, 9 March 1786., TCy. (Box-folder 1:1)
    - Sam. J. Harrison, Richmond to father, William Harrison, near Williamsburg, 1 July 1786., TCy. (Box-folder 1:1)
    - Sam. J. Harrison, Richmond to William Harrison, near Williamsburg, 21 September 1786., TCy. (Box-folder 1:1)
    - Christopher Anthony [n.p.] to William Harrison, York County, 17 February 1787., TCy. (Box-folder 1:1)
    - Sam. J. Harrison, Richmond to father William Harrison, York County, 28 August 1789., TCy. (Box-folder 1:1)
    - S. J. Harrison, Bedford, to father William Harrison, York County, 6 September 1789., TCy. (Box-folder 1:1)
    - S. J. Harrison, Bedford County, to father William Harrison, York County, 28 September 1789., TCy. (Box-folder 1:1)
  - Letters, 1890-1899., 66 items. (Box-folder 1:1-2)
    - S. J. Harrison, Lynchburg, to William Harrison, York City, 20 January 1790., TCy. (Box-folder 1:1)
    - S. J. Harrison, Goose Creek, to William Harrison, York County, 4 May 1790., TCy. (Box-folder 1:1)
    - Sam. J. Harrison, Lynchburg to William Harrison, York County, 10 October 1790., TCy. (Box-folder 1:1)
    - Sam. J. Harrison, Lynchburg, to father William Harrison, York City, 22 November 1790., TCy. (Box-folder 1:1)
    - Sam. J. Harrison, Lynchburg, to brother William Harrison, York County, 22 November 1790., TCy. (Box-folder 1:1)
    - S. J. Harrison, Lynchburg, to William Harrison, York County, 21 March 1791., TCy. (Box-folder 1:1)
    - Sam. J. Harrison, Lynchburg, to William Harrison, care Ro. Greenhow Esq. Williamsburg, 30 August 1791., TCy. (Box-folder 1:1)
    - Sam. J. Harrison, Lynchburg, to William Harrison, York County, 30 September 1791., TCy. (Box-folder 1:1)
    - Sam. J. Harrison, Lynchburg, to William Harrison Sr., York County, 20 November 1791., TCy. (Box-folder 1:1)
    - Sam. J. Harrison, Lynchburg, to William Harrison, York County, 6 January 1792., TCy. (Box-folder 1:1)
    - Christopher Anthony, Shingle Block, to William Harrison, York County, 12 February 1792., TCy. (Box-folder 1:1)
    - [Sam. J. Harrison Lynchburg, to [William Harrison], 21 February 1792., TCy. (Box-folder 1:1)
    - William Harrison, Jr., Lynchburg, to father, William Harrison, York County, 1 March 1792., TCy. (Box-folder 1:1)
    - Will. Harrison, Jr. to William Harrison, York County, 12 March 1792., TCy. (Box-folder 1:1)
    - Will. Harrison, Jr., Lynchburg, to William Harrison, 17 March 1792., TCy. (Box-folder 1:1)
    - W. Harrison, Jr. Lynchburg, to William Harrison, York County, 19 November 1792., TCy. (Box-folder 1:1)
    - Sam. J. Harrison, Lynchburg, to father [William Harrison], 25 November 1792., TCy. (Box-folder 1:1)
    - Wm. Harrison, Jr., Lynchburg, to William Harrison, York County, 15 December 1792., TCy. (Box-folder 1:1)
    - Sam. J. Harrison, Lynchburg, to father [William Harrison], 17 March 1793., TCy. (Box-folder 1:1)
    - Sam. J. Harrison, Lynchburg, to father [William] Harrison, York County, 11 May 1793., TCy. (Box-folder 1:1)
    - W. Harrison, Jr., Goose Creek, to father, William Harrison, York County, 15 August 1793., TCy. (Box-folder 1:1)
    - Sam. J. Harrison, Lynchburg, to William Harrison, care Ro. Greenhow, Williamsburg, 28 September 1793., TCy. (Box-folder 1:1)
    - Sam. J. Harrison, Lynchburg, to William Harrison, York County, 20 November 1793., TCy. (Box-folder 1:1)
    - Wm. Harrison, Jr., Goose Creek, to William Harrison York County, 1 December 1793., TCy. (Box-folder 1:1)
    - Wm. Harrison, Jr., Lynchburg, to father [William Harrison], 1 January 1794., TCy. (Box-folder 1:1)
    - Wm. Harrison, York County, to Samuel J. Harrison, Lynchburg, 12 May 1794., TCy. (Box-folder 1:1)
    - Wm. Harrison, Jr., Mountairy, Bedford County, to William Harrison, Skimino, York County, August 1794 [?]., TCy. (Box-folder 1:1)
    - Sam. Harrison, Richmond, to William Harrison Sr., York County, 29 August 1794., TCy. (Box-folder 1:1)
    - Sam. J. Harrison, Lynchburg, to William Harrison, York County, 18 September 1794., TCy. (Box-folder 1:1)
    - W. Harrison, Lynchburg, to father, William Harrison, York County, 22 January 1795., TCy. (Box-folder 1:1)
    - Sam. J. Harrison, Philadelphia, to William Harrison, care Robert Greenhow, Williamsburg, 27 April 1795., TCy. (Box-folder 1:1)
    - Wm. Harrison, Jr., Seneca, Campbell County, to William Harrison, York County, 20 September 1795., TCy. (Box-folder 1:1)
    - Sam. J. Harrison, Richmond to William Harrison Senr., care Ro. Greenhow, Williamsburg, 30 September 1795., TCy. (Box-folder 1:1)
    - Sam. J. Harrison, Lynchburg, to William Harrison, York County, 21 October 1795., TCy. (Box-folder 1:1)
    - Sam. J. Harrison, Richmond, to William Harrison, near Williamsburg, 5 November 1795., TCy. (Box-folder 1:1)
    - Sam. J. Harrison, Lynchburg, to William Harrison, near Williamsburg, 27 November 1795., TCy. (Box-folder 1:1)
    - Will. Harrison, Jr., Campbell, to William Harrison, care Robert Greenhow, Williamsburg, 15 January 1796., TCy. (Box-folder 1:1)
    - Sam. J. Harrison, Richmond, to William Harrison, Sr., near Williamsburg, 23 January 1796., TCy. (Box-folder 1:1)
    - Thomas Ladd, Ohms. City County, to Wm. Harrison, not addressed, 6 March 1796., TCy. (Box-folder 1:1)
    - W. Harrison, Lynchburg, to father [William Harrison], 16 March 1796., TCy. (Box-folder 1:1)
    - Sam. J. Harrison, Lynchburg, to William Harrison, near Williamsburg, 21 March 1796., TCy. (Box-folder 1:1)
    - Sam. J. Harrison, Richmond, to William Harrison, Sr., near Williamsburg, 4 June 1796., TCy. (Box-folder 1:1)
    - Sam. J. Harrison, Richmond, to William Harrison, near Williamsburg, 22 October 1796., TCy. (Box-folder 1:1)
    - Sam. J. Harrison, Richmond, to William Harrison, near Williamsburg, 22 December 1796., TCy. (Box-folder 1:1)
    - 27 February 1797. Sam. J. Harrison, Lynchburg, to William Harrison, near Williamsburg, TCy. (Box-folder 1:1)
    - W. Harrison, Jr., Seneca, Campbell County, to William Harrison, Skimininco, Williamsburg, York County, 6 March 1797., TCy. (Box-folder 1:1)
    - William Harrison, Jr., Seneca, Campbell County, to William Harrison, Skimminoe, York County, 10 April 1797., TCy. (Box-folder 1:1)
    - Sam. J. Harrison, Richmond, to William Harrison, near Williamsburg, 24 April 1797., TCy. (Box-folder 1:1)
    - Sam. J. Harrison, Lynchburg, to William Harrison, York County, 13 May 1797., TCy. (Box-folder 1:1)
    - Will. Harrison, Lynchburg, to William Harrison, Williamsburg, York County, 5 June 1797., TCy. (Box-folder 1:1)
    - Will. Harrison, Jr., Seneca, to William Harrison, Skimmino, York County, 1 August 1797., TCy. (Box-folder 1:1)
    - Sam. J. Harrison, Lynchburg, to William Harrison, Williamsburg, York County, 11 September 1797., TCy. (Box-folder 1:1)
    - Will. Harrison, Jr., Campbell County, to William Harrison, York County, 15 September 1797., TCy. (Box-folder 1:1)
    - Sam. J. Harrison, Lynchburg, to William Harrison, near Williamsburg, 11 December 1797., TCy. (Box-folder 1:1)
    - Sam. J. Harrison, Lynchburg, to William Harrison, Jr., York County, 21 February 1798., TCy. (Box-folder 1:2)
    - Sam. J. Harrison, Lynchburg, to William Harrison, near Williamsburg, 26 March 1798., TCy. (Box-folder 1:2)
    - W. Harrison, Lynchburg, to William Harrison, near Williamsburg, York County, 4 April 1798., TCy. (Box-folder 1:2)
    - Sam. J. Harrison, Richmond, to William Harrison near Williamsburg, 28 May 1798., TCy. (Box-folder 1:2)
    - W. Harrison, Richmond, to William Harrison, near Williamsburg, York County, 16 October 1798., TCy. (Box-folder 1:2)
    - Sam. J. Harrison, Lynchburg, to William Harrison, near Williamsburg, 29 February 1799., TCy. (Box-folder 1:2)
    - Sam. J. Harrison, Lynchburg, to William Harrison, near Williamsburg, 29 March 1799., TCy. (Box-folder 1:2)
    - Wm. Harrison, York County, to son Samuel J. Harrison, Lynchburg, 5 April 1799., TCy. (Box-folder 1:2)
    - Sam. J. Harrison, Lynchburg, to William Harrison, near Williamsburg, 5 July 1799., TCy. (Box-folder 1:2)
    - Sam. J. Harrison, Lynchburg, to William Harrison, near Williamsburg, 21 September 1799., TCy. (Box-folder 1:2)
    - Sam. J. Harrison, Lynchburg, to William Harrison, near Williamsburg, 19 November 1799., TCy. (Box-folder 1:2)
    - W. Harrison, Lynchburg, to William Harrison, near Williamsburg, 1 December 1799., TCy. (Box-folder 1:2)
  - Letters, 1800-1809., 76 items. (Box-folder 1:2-3)
    - Sam. J. Harrison, Lynchburg, to William Harrison, near Williamsburg, 17 January 1800., TCy. (Box-folder 1:2)
    - Sam. J. Harrison, Lynchburg, to father [William Harrison], 28 February 1800., TCy. (Box-folder 1:2)
    - W. Harrison, Jr., Lynchburg, to William Harrison, near Williamsburg, 28 February 1800., TCy. (Box-folder 1:2)
    - Sam. J. Harrison, Lynchburg, to William Harrison, near Williamsburg, 9 May 1800., TCy. (Box-folder 1:2)
    - Sam. J. Harrison, Lynchburg, to William Harrison, near Williamsburg, 20 June 1800., TCy. (Box-folder 1:2)
    - Sam. J. Harrison, Lynchburg, to William Harrison, near Williamsburg, 18 July 1800., TCy. (Box-folder 1:2)
    - Sam. J. Harrison, Lynchburg, to William Harrison, near Williamsburg, 15 August 1800., TCy. (Box-folder 1:2)
    - Wm. Harrison, Jr., Lynchburg, to William Harrison, Sr., near Williamsburg, 22 August 1800., TCy. (Box-folder 1:2)
    - Sam. J. Harrison, Richmond, to William Harrison, near Williamsburg, 14 October 1800., TCy. (Box-folder 1:2)
    - Sam. J. Harrison, Lynchburg, to William Harrison, near Williamsburg, 16 January 1801., TCy. (Box-folder 1:2)
    - Sam. J. Harrison, Lynchburg, to William Harrison, near Williamsburg, 26 March 1801., TCy. (Box-folder 1:2)
    - Will. Harrison, Jr., Campbell, to William Harrison, near Williamsburg, 28 May 1801., TCy. (Box-folder 1:2)
    - Wm. Harrison, York County, to son Samuel, 5 August 1801., TCy. (Box-folder 1:2)
    - Sam. J. Harrison, Richmond, to William Harrison, near Williamsburg, 9 October 1801., TCy. (Box-folder 1:2)
    - Wm. Harrison, Lynchburg, to William Harrison, near Williamsburg, 3 February 1802., TCy. (Box-folder 1:2)
    - Sam. J. Harrison, Richmond, to William Harrison, near Williamsburg, 24 June 1802., TCy. (Box-folder 1:2)
    - Sam. J. Harrison, Lynchburg, to William Harrison, near Williamsburg, 1 August 1802., TCy. (Box-folder 1:2)
    - Sam. J. Harrison, Lynchburg, to William Harrison, near Williamsburg, 10 December 1802., TCy. (Box-folder 1:2)
    - Wm. Harrison, Jr., Lynchburg, to William Harrison, Sr., near Williamsburg, 9 January 1803., TCy. (Box-folder 1:2)
    - Wm. Harrison, Jr., Lynchburg, to William Harrison, Sr., near Williamsburg, 30 April 1803., TCy. (Box-folder 1:2)
    - Sam. J. Harrison, Lynchburg, to William Harrison, near Williamsburg, 8 May 1803., TCy. (Box-folder 1:2)
    - Sam. J. Harrison, Richmond, to William Harrison, York County, 19 May 1803., TCy. (Box-folder 1:2)
    - S. J. Harrison, Lynchburg, to William Harrison, near Williamsburg, 7 August 1503., TCy. (Box-folder 1:2)
    - Wm. Harrison, Lynchburg, to William Harrison, near Williamsburg, 11 August 1803., TCy. (Box-folder 1:2)
    - S. J. Harrison, Richmond, to William Harrison, near Williamsburg, 2 October 1803., TCy. (Box-folder 1:2)
    - Wm. Harrison, Lynchburg, to Wm. Harrison, near Williamsburg, 12 December 1803., TCy. (Box-folder 1:2)
    - Wm. Harrison, Lynchburg, to Jordan Harrison, near Williamsburg, 1 January 1804., TCy. (Box-folder 1:2)
    - Wm. Harrison, Lynchburg, to Jordan Harrison, near Williamsburg, 28 May 1804., TCy. (Box-folder 1:2)
    - Wm. Harrison, Lynchburg, to William Harrison, near Williamsburg, 29 May 1804., TCy. (Box-folder 1:2)
    - Wm. Harrison, Richmond, to William Harrison, near Williamsburg, 13 August 1804., TCy. (Box-folder 1:2)
    - Wm. Harrison, Richmond, to William Harrison, near Williamsburg, 24 October 1804., TCy. (Box-folder 1:2)
    - Wm. Harrison, Richmond, to William Harrison, near Williamsburg, 30 March 1804., TCy. (Box-folder 1:2)
    - S. J. Harrison, Richmond, to William Harrison, near Williamsburg, 2 May l805., TCy. (Box-folder 1:2)
    - Wm. Harrison, Lynchburg, to William Harrison, near Williamsburg, 27 June 1805., TCy. (Box-folder 1:2)
    - S. J. Harrison, Richmond, to William Harrison, near Williamsburg, 10 August 1805., TCy. (Box-folder 1:2)
    - S. J. Harrison, Richmond, to William Harrison, near Williamsburg, 11 October 1805., TCy. (Box-folder 1:2)
    - Wm. Harrison, Richmond, to William Harrison, Sr., near Williamsburg, 14 October 1805., TCy. (Box-folder 1:2)
    - Wm. Harrison, Lynchburg, to Jordan Harrison, near Williamsburg, 5 January 1806., TCy. (Box-folder 1:2)
    - S. J. Harrison, Lynchburg, to William Harrison, near Williamsburg, 20 April 1806., TCy. (Box-folder 1:2)
    - S. J. Harrison, Lynchburg, to William Harrison, near Williamsburg, 12 May 1806., TCy. (Box-folder 1:2)
    - Wm. Harrison, Lynchburg, to William Harrison, Sr., near Williamsburg, 3 August l806., TCy. (Box-folder 1:2)
    - S. J. Harrison, Lynchburg, to William Harrison, near Williamsburg, 31 August 1806., TCy. (Box-folder 1:2)
    - S. J. Harrison, Lynchburg, to William Harrison, near Williamsburg, 5 October 1806., TCy. (Box-folder 1:2)
    - Wm. Harrison, Jr., Lynchburg, to Jordan Harrison, near Williamsburg, 12 October 1806., TCy. (Box-folder 1:2)
    - S. J. Harrison, Richmond, to William Harrison, near Williamsburg, 6 November 1806., TCy. (Box-folder 1:2)
    - S. J. Harrison, Lynchburg, to Jordan Harrison, near Williamsburg, 15 November 1806., TCy. (Box-folder 1:2)
    - S. J. Harrison, Lynchburg, to William Harrison, near Williamsburg, 28 November 1806., TCy. (Box-folder 1:2)
    - Wm. Harrison, Lynchburg, to William Harrison, near Williamsburg, 13 February 1807., TCy. (Box-folder 1:3)
    - S. J. Harrison, Lynchburg, to William Harrison, near Williamsburg, 15 February 1807., TCy. (Box-folder 1:3)
    - S. J. Harrison, Lynchburg, to William Harrison, near Williamsburg, 23 May 1807., TCy. (Box-folder 1:3)
    - Wm. Harrison, Lynchburg, to Jordan Harrison, near Williamsburg, 23 May 1807., TCy. (Box-folder 1:3)
    - S. J. Harrison, Richmond, To William Harrison, York County, 10 July 1807., TCy. (Box-folder 1:3)
    - Wm. Harrison, Richmond, to Jordan Harrison, near Williamsburg, 22 July 1807., TCy. (Box-folder 1:3)
    - Wm. Harrison, Richmond, to Jordan Harrison, near Williamsburg, 22 July 1807., TCy. (Box-folder 1:3)
    - S. J. Harrison, Lynchburg, to William Harrison, near Williamsburg, 8 August 1807., TCy. (Box-folder 1:3)
    - S. J. Harrison, Lynchburg, to William Harrison, near Williamsburg, 5 September 1807., TCy. (Box-folder 1:3)
    - Wm. Harrison, Lynchburg, to Jordan Harrison, near Williamsburg, 23 September 1807., TCy. (Box-folder 1:3)
    - Wm. Harrison, Richmond, to William Harrison, near Williamsburg, 7 December 1807., TCy. (Box-folder 1:3)
    - S. J. Harrison, Lynchburg, to brother, no address on letter, 9 January 1808., TCy. (Box-folder 1:3)
    - Wm. Harrison, Jr., Seneca, to Jordan Harrison, near Williamsburg, 23 January 1808., TCy. (Box-folder 1:3)
    - S. J. Harrison, Lynchburg, to William Harrison, near Williamsburg, 9 April 1808., TCy. (Box-folder 1:3)
    - S. J. Harrison, Richmond, to William Harrison, near Williamsburg, 29 June 1808., TCy. (Box-folder 1:3)
    - Wm. Harrison, Jr., Campbell, to William Harrison, Sr., near Williamsburg, 20 July 1808., TCy. (Box-folder 1:3)
    - S. J. Harrison, Lynchburg, to William Harrison, near Williamsburg, 6 August 1808., TCy. (Box-folder 1:3)
    - Wm. Harrison, Richmond, to William Harrison, Sr., near Williamsburg, 26 August 1808., TCy. (Box-folder 1:3)
    - S. J. Harrison, Lynchburg, to William Harrison, near Williamsburg, 24 September 1808., TCy. (Box-folder 1:3)
    - S. J. Harrison, Lynchburg, to William Harrison, near Williamsburg, 22 October 1808., TCy. (Box-folder 1:3)
    - S. J. Harrison, Lynchburg, to William Harrison, n.p., 7 February 1809., TCy. (Box-folder 1:3)
    - Wm. Harrison, Lynchburg, to William Harrison, near Williamsburg, 23 March 1809., TCy. (Box-folder 1:3)
    - W. Harrison, Lynchburg, to brother Jordan, no address, 25 March 1809., TCy. (Box-folder 1:3)
    - S. J. Harrison, Richmond, to William Harrison, near Williamsburg, 26 March 1809., TCy. (Box-folder 1:3)
    - S. J. Harrison, Richmond, to William Harrison, near Williamsburg, 2 June 1809., TCy. (Box-folder 1:3)
    - S. J. Harrison, Richmond, to William Harrison, near Williamsburg, 16 June 1809., TCy. (Box-folder 1:3)
    - Jordan Harrison, York County, to William Harrison, Lynchburg, 4 July 1809., TCy. (Box-folder 1:3)
    - Wm. Harrison, Lynchburg, to Jordan Harrison, near Williamsburg, 9 July 1809., TCy. (Box-folder 1:3)
    - S. J. Harrison, Lynchburg, to Jordan Harrison, near Williamsburg, 21 August 1809., TCy. (Box-folder 1:3)
  - Letters, 1810-1819., 35 items. (Box-folder 1:3-4)
    - Wm. Harrison, Lynchburg, to Jordan Harrison, near Williamsburg, 14 January 1810., TCy. (Box-folder 1:3)
    - Wm. Harrison, Jr., Lynchburg, to Jordan Harrison, near Williamsburg, 28 January 1810., TCy. (Box-folder 1:3)
    - Wm. Harrison, Lynchburg, to Jordan Harrison, near Williamsburg, 26 February 1810., TCy. (Box-folder 1:3)
    - S. J. Harrison, Lynchburg, to William Harrison, near Williamsburg, 19 March 1810., TCy. (Box-folder 1:3)
    - S. J. Harrison, Richmond, to William Harrison, near Williamsburg, 1 May 1810., TCy. (Box-folder 1:3)
    - Wm. Harrison, Lynchburg, to William Harrison, York County, 1 May 1810., TCy. (Box-folder 1:3)
    - Wm. Harrison, Lynchburg, to William Harrison, near Williamsburg, 8 July 1810., TCy. (Box-folder 1:3)
    - Wm. Harrison, Lynchburg, to Jordan Harrison, near Williamsburg, 30 July 1810., TCy. (Box-folder 1:3)
    - S. J. Harrison, Richmond, to William Harrison, Williamsburg, 21 December 1810., TCy. (Box-folder 1:3)
    - Wm. Harrison, Lynchburg, to Jordan Harrison, near Williamsburg, 7 January 1811., TCy. (Box-folder 1:4)
    - Wm. Harrison, Lynchburg, to Jordan Harrison, near Williamsburg, 7 April 1811., TCy. (Box-folder 1:4)
    - S. J. Harrison, Richmond, to Jordan Harrison, Williamsburg, 26 May 1811., TCy. (Box-folder 1:4)
    - W. Harrison, Lynchburg, to William Harrison, near Williamsburg, 13 July 1811., TCy. (Box-folder 1:4)
    - Jordan Harrison, Lynchburg, to William Harrison, near Williamsburg, 11 August 1811., TCy. (Box-folder 1:4)
    - S. J. Harrison, Lynchburg, to William Harrison, 1 September 1811., TCy. (Box-folder 1:4)
      Address is torn off.
    - S. J. Harrison, Lynchburg, to Jordan Harrison, Williamsburg, 4 December 1811., TCy. (Box-folder 1:4)
    - S. J. Harrison, Richmond, to William Harrison, Williamsburg, 11 April 1812., TCy. (Box-folder 1:4)
    - W. Harrison, Lynchburg, to William Harrison, near Williamsburg, 26 April 1812., TCy. (Box-folder 1:4)
    - W. Harrison, Lynchburg, to Jordan Harrison, Williamsburg, 13 September 1812., TCy. (Box-folder 1:4)
    - Robert J. Harrison, Lynchburg, to his uncle Jordan Harrison, near Williamsburg, 10 October 1812., TCy. (Box-folder 1:4)
    - W. Harrison, Lynchburg, to William Harrison, near Williamsburg, 12 October 1812., TCy. (Box-folder 1:4)
    - Robert J. Harrison, Lynchburg, to his father, Samuel J. Harrison, Richmond, 21 October 1812., TCy. (Box-folder 1:4)
    - W. Harrison, Lynchburg, to his brother Jordan Harrison near Williamsburg, 15 November 1812., TCy. (Box-folder 1:4)
    - William Harrison, Jr. to William Harrison, Sr., near Williamsburg, 27 November 1813., TCy. (Box-folder 1:4)
    - Margaret Harrison, York County, to her brother Jordan Harrison, Lynchburg, 13 July 1814., TCy. (Box-folder 1:4)
    - William Harrison, Lynchburg, to William Harrison, near Williamsburg, 20 July 1814., TCy. (Box-folder 1:4)
    - Robert Jordan Harrison, Lynchburg, to his uncle Jordan Harrison, near Williamsburg, 2 June l8l5., TCy. (Box-folder 1:4)
    - Deborah Harrison, York County, to her brother Jordan Harrison, Lynchburg, 22 September 1815., TCy. (Box-folder 1:4)
    - R. Harris [?], Green Meadow, to Ruth Harrison, York County, 2 June 1816., TCy. (Box-folder 1:4)
    - Jordan Harrison, Richmond, to William Harrison, near Williamsburg, 20 September 1816., TCy. (Box-folder 1:4)
    - S. J. Harrison, Lynchburg, to William Harrison, Sr. near Williamsburg, 6 April 1817., TCy. (Box-folder 1:4)